(Raj:)Like a Jet Ski.
(Howard:)Why do you want a Jet Ski?
(Raj:)All the wealthy and beautiful people
in movies ride Jet Skis.
(Raj:)-That can't just be a coincidence.
HOWARD: Ugh.
(Sheldon:)We can't sell it. We have to keep it
and love it and polish it.
(Sheldon:)Take it out occasionally
when we go to the park...
...and reenact our favorite scenes
from the movies.
(Howard:)It's sad how great that sounds.
[HOWARD CHUCKLES]
(Leonard:)Guys, it's stolen.
It should go back to Peter Jackson.
(Leonard:)-He made the movies. It belongs to him.
HOWARD: Fine.
(Howard:)He can have it back.
(Howard:)As long as he promises to make me
a hobbit in his next movie.
But there are no Jewish hobbits.
(Howard:)Clearly, you've never been to my house
for dinner on Rosh Hashanah.
(Leonard:)We are not blackmailing Peter--
(Leonard:)-All right, where's the ring?
-You mean my ring?
(Leonard:)-What are you doing?
-The ring was unguarded.
It was sitting on the table.
Anyone could've taken it.
(Sheldon:)Proof? I did.
(Leonard:)Give me that.
Be reasonable. We want to do
different things with the ring.